Guide to the Sunset Magazine Records M2065
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Photograph files
  - 4-68-181 to 4-68-238, 1968-04 (Box 189, Folder 3)
  - 4-68-240 to 4-68-323, 1968-04 (Box 189, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1968-05 (Box 189, Folder 5)
  - May 1968 Central magazine (Box 189, Folder 6)
  - 5-68-001 to 5-68-072, 1968-05 (Box 190, Folder 1)
  - 5-68-073 to 5-68-123, 1968-05 (Box 190, Folder 2)
  - 5-68-124 to 5-68-187, 1968-05 (Box 190, Folder 3)
  - 5-68-189 to 5-68-235, 1968-05 (Box 190, Folder 4)
  - 5-68-236 to 5-68-278, 1968-05 (Box 190, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1968-06 (Box 190, Folder 6)
  - June 1968 Central magazine (Box 190, Folder 7)
  - 6-68-001 to 6-68-092, 1968-06 (Box 191, Folder 1)
  - 6-68-093 to 6-68-121, 1968-06 (Box 191, Folder 2)
  - 6-68-122 to 6-68-190, 1968-06 (Box 191, Folder 3)
  - 6-68-200 to 6-68-277, 1968-06 (Box 191, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1968-07 (Box 191, Folder 5)
  - July 1968 Central magazine (Box 191, Folder 6)
  - 7-68-001 to 7-68-040, 1968-07 (Box 191, Folder 7)
  - 7-68-041 to 7-68-100, 1968-07 (Box 192, Folder 1)
  - 7-68-101 to 7-68-156, 1968-07 (Box 192, Folder 2)
  - 7-68-157 to 7-68-217, 1968-07 (Box 192, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1968-08 (Box 192, Folder 4)
  - August 1968 Central magazine (Box 192, Folder 5)
  - 8-68-001 to 8-68-073, 1968-08 (Box 192, Folder 6)
  - 8-68-074 to 8-68-136, 1968-08 (Box 192, Folder 7)
  - 8-68-137 to 8-68-196, 1968-08 (Box 193, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1968-09 (Box 193, Folder 2)
  - September 1968 Central magazine, 1968-09 (Box 193, Folder 3)
  - 9-68-001 to 9-68-068, 1968-09 (Box 193, Folder 4)
  - 9-68-069 to 9-68-124, 1968-09 (Box 193, Folder 5)
  - 9-68-125 to 9-68-182, 1968-09 (Box 193, Folder 6)
  - 9-68-183 to 9-68-220, 1968-09 (Box 193, Folder 7)
  - 9-68-221 to 9-68-278, 1968-09 (Box 194, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1968-10 (Box 194, Folder 2)
  - October 1968 Central magazine (Box 194, Folder 3)
  - 10-68-001 to 10-68-067, 1968-10 (Box 194, Folder 4)
  - 10-68-069 to 10-68-129, 1968-10 (Box 194, Folder 5)
  - 10-68-130 to 10-68-189, 1968-10 (Box 194, Folder 6)
  - 10-68-191 to 10-68-234, 1968-10 (Box 194, Folder 7)
  - 10-68-235 to 10-68-279, 1968-10 (Box 195, Folder 1)
  - 10-68-281 to 10-68-328, 1968-10 (Box 195, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1968-11 (Box 195, Folder 3)
  - November 1968 Central magazine (Box 195, Folder 4)
  - 11-68-001 to 11-68-058, 1968-11 (Box 195, Folder 5)
  - 11-68-059 to 11-68-113, 1968-11 (Box 195, Folder 6)
  - 11-68-114 to 11-68-177, 1968-11 (Box 195, Folder 7)
  - 11-68-179 to 11-68-243, 1968-11 (Box 196, Folder 1)
  - 11-68-244 to 11-68-315, 1968-11 (Box 196, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1968-12 (Box 196, Folder 3)
  - December 1968 Central magazine (Box 196, Folder 4)
  - 12-68-000 to 12-68-068, 1968-12 (Box 196, Folder 5)
  - 12-68-069 to 12-68-123, 1968-12 (Box 196, Folder 6)
  - 12-68-124 to 12-68-169, 1968-12 (Box 197, Folder 1)
  - 12-68-171 to 12-68-231, 1968-12 (Box 197, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1968-12 (Box 197, Folder 3)
  - January 1969 Central magazine (Box 197, Folder 4)
  - 1-69-000 to 1-69-078, 1969-01 (Box 197, Folder 5)
  - 1-69-079 to 1-69-142, 1969-01 (Box 197, Folder 6)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1969-01 (Box 197, Folder 7)
  - February 1969 Central magazine, 1969-01 (Box 197, Folder 8)
  - 2-69-000 to 2-69-062, 1969-02 (Box 198, Folder 1)
  - 2-69-063 to 2-69-115, 1969-02 (Box 198, Folder 2)
  - 2-69-116 to 2-69-171, 1969-02 (Box 198, Folder 3)
  - 2-69-172 to 2-69-216, with Contact sheets, 1969-02 (Box 198, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1969-03 (Box 198, Folder 5)
  - March 1969 Central magazine (Box 198, Folder 6)
  - 3-69-000 to 3-69-053, 1969-03 (Box 198, Folder 7)
  - 3-69-054 to 3-69-118, 1969-03 (Box 199, Folder 1)
  - 3-69-119 to 3-69-172, 1969-03 (Box 199, Folder 2)
  - 3-69-173 to 3-69-253, 1969-03 (Box 199, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1969-04 (Box 199, Folder 4)
  - April 1969 Central magazine (Box 199, Folder 5)
  - 4-69-000 to 4-69-062, 1969-04 (Box 199, Folder 6)
  - 4-69-063 to 4-69-126, 1969-04 (Box 200, Folder 1)
  - 4-69-127 to 4-69-189, 1969-04 (Box 200, Folder 2)
  - 4-69-190 to 4-69-239, 1969-04 (Box 200, Folder 3)
  - 4-69-240 to 4-69-281, 1969-04 (Box 200, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1969-04 (Box 200, Folder 5)
  - May 1969 Central magazine (Box 200, Folder 6)
  - 5-69-000 to 5-69-075, 1969-05 (Box 200, Folder 7)
  - 5-69-078 to 5-69-152, 1969-05 (Box 201, Folder 1)
  - 5-69-153 to 5-69-205, 1969-05 (Box 201, Folder 2)
  - 5-69-207 to 5-69-264, 1969-05 (Box 201, Folder 3)
  - 5-69-267 to 5-69-328, 1969-05 (Box 201, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1969-06 (Box 201, Folder 5)
  - June 1969 Central magazine (Box 201, Folder 6)
  - 6-69-000 to 6-69-072, 1969-06 (Box 202, Folder 1)
  - 6-69-073 to 6-69-141 includes some negatives and contact sheets, 1969-06 (Box 202, Folder 2)
  - 6-69-143 to 6-69-211, 1969-06 (Box 202, Folder 3)
  - 6-69-213 to 6-69-286, 1969-06 (Box 202, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1969-06 (Box 202, Folder 5)
  - July 1969 Central magazine (Box 202, Folder 6)
  - 7-69-000 to 7-69-054, 1969-07 (Box 203, Folder 1)
  - 7-69-055 to 7-69-127 includes one contact sheet, 1969-07 (Box 203, Folder 2)
  - 7-69-132 to 7-69-205, 1969-07 (Box 203, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1969-08 (Box 203, Folder 4)
  - August 1969 Central magazine (Box 203, Folder 5)
  - 8-69-000 to 8-69-078, 1969-08 (Box 203, Folder 6)
  - 8-69-080 to 8-69-163, 1969-08 (Box 204, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1969-09 (Box 204, Folder 2)
  - September 1969 Central magazine (Box 204, Folder 3)
  - 9-69-001 to 9-69-068, 1969-09 (Box 204, Folder 4)
  - 9-69-069 to 9-69-124, 1969-09 (Box 204, Folder 5)
  - 9-69-125 to 9-69-183, 1969-09 (Box 204, Folder 6)
  - 9-69-185 to 9-69-234, 1969-09 (Box 205, Folder 1)
  - 9-69-235 to 9-69-271, 1969-09 (Box 205, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1969-10 (Box 205, Folder 3)
  - October 1969 Central magazine (Box 205, Folder 4)
  - 10-69-001 to 10-69-084, 1969-10 (Box 205, Folder 5)
  - 10-69-085 to 10-69-155, 1969-10 (Box 205, Folder 6)
  - 10-69-157 to 10-69-217, 1969-10 (Box 205, Folder 7)
  - 10-69-220 to 10-69-266, 1969-10 (Box 206, Folder 1)
  - 10-69-267 to 10-69-319, 1969-10 (Box 206, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1969-11 (Box 206, Folder 3)
  - November 1969 Central magazine (Box 206, Folder 4)
  - 11-69-000 to 11-69-064, 1969-11 (Box 206, Folder 5)
  - 11-69-065 to 11-69-130, 1969-11 (Box 206, Folder 6)
  - 11-69-131 to 11-63-194, 1969-11 (Box 206, Folder 7)
  - 11-69-195 to 11-69-251, 1969-11 (Box 207, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1969-12 (Box 207, Folder 2)
  - December 1969 Central magazine (Box 207, Folder 3)
  - 12-69-000 to 12-69-060, 1969-12 (Box 207, Folder 4)
  - 12-69-062 to 12-69-112, 1969-12 (Box 207, Folder 5)
  - 12-69-113 to 12-69-171, 1969-12 (Box 207, Folder 6)
  - 12-69-172 to 12-69-203, 1969-12 (Box 207, Folder 7)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1977-01 (Box 208, Folder 1)
  - January 1977 Central magazine (Box 208, Folder 2)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1977-01 (Box 208, Folder 3)
  - 1-77-001 to 1-77-061, 1977-01 (Box 208, Folder 4)
  - 1-77-062 to 1-77-123, 1977-01 (Box 208, Folder 5)
  - 1-77-124 to 1-77-194, 1977-01 (Box 208, Folder 6)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1977-02 (Box 208, Folder 7)
  - February 1977 Central magazine (Box 208, Folder 8)
  - Negatives, 1977-02 (Box 208, Folder 9)
  - 2-77-001 to 2-77-055, 1977-02 (Box 209, Folder 1)
  - 2-77-056 to 2-77-118, 1977-02 (Box 209, Folder 2)
  - 2-77-121 to 2-77-180, 1977-02 (Box 209, Folder 3)
  - 2-77-181 to 2-77-231, 1977-02 (Box 209, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1977-03 (Box 209, Folder 5)
  - March 1977 Central magazine (Box 209, Folder 6)
  - Negatives, 1977-03 (Box 209, Folder 7)
  - 3-77-001 to 3-77-061, 1977-03 (Box 210, Folder 1)
  - 3-77-063 to 3-77-120, 1977-03 (Box 210, Folder 2)
  - 3-77-122 to 3-77-189, 1977-03 (Box 210, Folder 3)
  - 3-77-190 to 3-77-254, 1977-03 (Box 210, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1977-04 (Box 210, Folder 5)
  - April 1977 Central magazine (Box 210, Folder 6)
  - Negatives, 1977-04 (Box 210, Folder 7)
  - 4-77-001 to 4-77-064, 1977-04 (Box 211, Folder 1)
  - 4-77-065 to 4-77-134, 1977-04 (Box 211, Folder 2)
  - 4-77-135 to 4-77-206, 1977-04 (Box 211, Folder 3)
  - 4-77-208 to 4-77-274, 1977-04 (Box 211, Folder 4)
  - 4-77-275 to 4-77-327, 1977-04 (Box 211, Folder 5)
  - 4-77-328 to 4-77-380, 1977-04 (Box 212, Folder 1)
  - 4-77-381 to 4-77-429, 1977-04 (Box 212, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1977-05 (Box 212, Folder 3)
  - May 1977 Central magazine (Box 212, Folder 4)
  - Slides, 1977-05 (Box 212, Folder 5)
  - 5-77-001 to 5-77-068, 1977-05 (Box 212, Folder 6)
  - 5-77-069 to 5-77-130, 1977-05 (Box 212, Folder 7)
  - 5-77-131 to 5-77-194, 1977-05 (Box 213, Folder 1)
  - 5-77-195 to 5-77-256, 1977-05 (Box 213, Folder 2)
  - 5-77-257 to 5-77-320, 1977-05 (Box 213, Folder 3)
  - 5-77-322 to 5-77-388, 1977-05 (Box 213, Folder 4)
  - Negatives, 1977-06 (Box 213, Folder 5)
  - 6-77-001 to 6-77-061, 1977-06 (Box 214, Folder 1)
  - 6-77-062 to 6-77-129, 1977-06 (Box 214, Folder 2)
  - 6-77-131 to 6-77-193, 1977-06 (Box 214, Folder 3)
  - 6-77-194 to 6-77-261, 1977-06 (Box 214, Folder 4)
  - 6-77-262 to 6-77-328, 1977-06 (Box 214, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1977-07 (Box 215, Folder 1)
  - July 1977 Central (Box 215, Folder 2)
  - Slides, 1977-07 (Box 215, Folder 3)
  - 7-77-001 to 7-77-065, 1977-07 (Box 215, Folder 4)
  - 7-77-066 to 7-77-117, 1977-07 (Box 215, Folder 5)
  - 7-77-119 to 7-77-179, 1977-07 (Box 215, Folder 6)
  - 7-77-180 to 7-77-236, 1977-07 (Box 215, Folder 7)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1977-08 (Box 215, Folder 8)
  - August 1977 Central magazine (Box 215, Folder 9)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1977-08 (Box 216, Folder 1)
  - 8-77-001 to 8-77-055, 1977-08 (Box 216, Folder 2)
  - 8-77-056 to 8-77-105, 1977-08 (Box 216, Folder 3)
  - 8-77-106 to 8-77-160, 1977-08 (Box 216, Folder 4)
  - 8-77-161 to 8-77-216, 1977-08 (Box 216, Folder 5)
  - 8-77-217 to 8-77-274, 1977-08 (Box 216, Folder 6)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1977-09 (Box 217, Folder 1)
  - September 1977 Central magazine (Box 217, Folder 2)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1977-09 (Box 217, Folder 3)
  - 9-77-001 to 9-77-064, 1977-09 (Box 217, Folder 4)
  - 9-77-065 to 9-77-114, 1977-09 (Box 217, Folder 5)
  - 9-77-115 to 9-77-163, 1977-09 (Box 217, Folder 6)
  - 9-77-164 to 9-77-216, 1977-09 (Box 217, Folder 7)
  - 9-77-217 to 9-77-268, 1977-09 (Box 218, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1977-10 (Box 218, Folder 2)
  - October 1977 Central magazine (Box 218, Folder 3)
  - Transparencies, 1977-10 (Box 218, Folder 4)
  - 10-77-000 to 10-77-056, 1977-10 (Box 218, Folder 5)
  - 10-77-057 to 10-77-122, 1977-10 (Box 218, Folder 6)
  - 10-77-123 to 10-77-178, 1977-10 (Box 218, Folder 7)
  - 10-77-179 to 10-77-244, 1977-10 (Box 219, Folder 1)
  - 10-77-245 to 10-77-296, 1977-10 (Box 219, Folder 2)
  - 10-77-297 to 10-77-363, 1977-10 (Box 219, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1977-11 (Box 219, Folder 4)
  - November 1977 Central magazine (Box 219, Folder 5)
  - Slides and Negatives, 1977-11 (Box 219, Folder 6)
  - 11-77-001 to 11-77-057, 1977-11 (Box 219, Folder 7)
  - 11-77-058 to 11-77-113, 1977-11 (Box 220, Folder 1)
  - 11-77-114 to 11-77-173, 1977-11 (Box 220, Folder 2)
  - 11-77-174 to 11-77-234, 1977-11 (Box 220, Folder 3)
  - 11-77-235 to 11-77-274, 1977-11 (Box 220, Folder 4)
  - 11-77-276 to 11-77-313, 1977-11 (Box 220, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1977-12 (Box 220, Folder 6)
  - December 1977 Central magazine (Box 220, Folder 7)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1977-12 (Box 221, Folder 1)
  - 12-77-001 to 12-77-062, 1977-12 (Box 221, Folder 2)
  - 12-77-063 to 12-77-129, 1977-12 (Box 221, Folder 3)
  - 12-77-130 to 12-77-187, 1977-12 (Box 221, Folder 4)
  - 12-77-188 to 12-77-253, 1977-12 (Box 221, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1978-01 (Box 221, Folder 6)
  - January 1978 Central magazine (Box 221, Folder 7)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1978-01 (Box 221, Folder 8)
  - 1-78-001 to 1-78-053, 1978-01 (Box 222, Folder 1)
  - 1-78-054 to 1-78-101, 1978-01 (Box 222, Folder 2)
  - 1-78-103 to 1-78-146, 1978-01 (Box 222, Folder 3)
  - 1-78-147 to 1-78-193, 1978-01 (Box 222, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1978-02 (Box 222, Folder 5)
  - February 1978 Central magazine (Box 222, Folder 6)
  - Slides and transparency, 1978-02 (Box 222, Folder 7)
  - 2-78-001 to 2-78-062, 1978-02 (Box 222, Folder 8)
  - 2-78-063 to 2-78-118, 1978-02 (Box 223, Folder 1)
  - 2-78-119 to 2-78-178, 1978-02 (Box 223, Folder 2)
  - 2-78-180 to 2-78-230, 1978-02 (Box 223, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1978-03 (Box 223, Folder 4)
  - March 1978 Central magazine (Box 223, Folder 5)
  - 3-78-001 to 3-78-067, 1978-03 (Box 223, Folder 6)
  - 3-78-068 to 3-78-131, 1978-03 (Box 224, Folder 1)
  - 3-78-132 to 3-78-190, 1978-03 (Box 224, Folder 2)
  - 3-78-191 to 3-78-246, 1978-03 (Box 224, Folder 3)
  - 3-78-247 to 3-78-304, 1978-03 (Box 224, Folder 4)
  - 3-78-306 to 3-78-365, 1978-03 (Box 224, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1978-04 (Box 225, Folder 1)
  - April 1978 Central magazine (Box 225, Folder 2)
  - Memorandums, Slides, transparencies, 1978-04 (Box 225, Folder 3)
  - 4-78-001 to 4-78-065, 1978-04 (Box 225, Folder 4)
  - 4-78-066 to 4-78-131, 1978-04 (Box 225, Folder 5)
  - 4-78-132 to 4-78-188, 1978-04 (Box 225, Folder 6)
  - 4-78-189 to 4-78-247, 1978-04 (Box 226, Folder 1)
  - 4-78-248 to 4-78-313, 1978-04 (Box 226, Folder 2)
  - 4-78-315 to 4-78-367, 1978-04 (Box 226, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1978-05 (Box 226, Folder 4)
  - May 1978 Central magazine (Box 226, Folder 5)
  - Memorandum, Slides, and transparency, 1978-05 (Box 226, Folder 6)
  - 5-78-001 to 5-78-062, 1978-05 (Box 226, Folder 7)
  - 5-78-064 to 5-78-126, 1978-05 (Box 227, Folder 1)
  - 5-78-128 to 5-78-192, 1978-05 (Box 227, Folder 2)
  - 5-78-193 to 5-78-245, 1978-05 (Box 227, Folder 3)
  - 5-78-246 to 5-78-298, 1978-05 (Box 227, Folder 4)
  - 5-78-299 to 5-78-342, 1978-05 (Box 227, Folder 5)
  - 5-78-344 to 5-78-402, 1978-05 (Box 228, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1978-06 (Box 228, Folder 2)
  - June 1978 Central magazine (Box 228, Folder 3)
  - Slides, transparencies, and negatives, 1978-06 (Box 228, Folder 4)
  - 6-78-001 to 6-78-067, 1978-06 (Box 228, Folder 5)
  - 6-78-001 to 6-78-067, 1978-06 (Box 228, Folder 6)
  - 6-78-123 to 6-78-181, 1978-06 (Box 228, Folder 7)
  - 6-78-182 to 6-78-233, 1978-06 (Box 229, Folder 1)
  - 6-78-234 to 6-78-294, 1978-06 (Box 229, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1978-07 (Box 229, Folder 3)
  - July 1978 Central magazine (Box 229, Folder 4)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1978-07 (Box 229, Folder 5)
  - 7-78-001 to 7-78-062, 1978-07 (Box 229, Folder 6)
  - 7-78-063 to 7-78-123, 1978-07 (Box 229, Folder 7)
  - 7-78-124 to 7-78-181, 1978-07 (Box 230, Folder 1)
  - 7-78-183 to 7-78-227, 1978-07 (Box 230, Folder 2)
  - 7-78-228 to 7-78-269, 1978-07 (Box 230, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1978-08 (Box 230, Folder 4)
  - August 1978 Central magazine (Box 230, Folder 5)
  - Slides, transparency and color photographs, 1978-08 (Box 230, Folder 6)
  - 8-78-001 to 8-78-065, 1978-08 (Box 230, Folder 7)
  - 8-78-067 to 8-78-121, 1978-08 (Box 231, Folder 1)
  - 8-78-123 to 8-78-178, 1978-08 (Box 231, Folder 2)
  - 8-78-179 to 8-78-238, 1978-08 (Box 231, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1978-09 (Box 231, Folder 4)
  - September 1978 Central magazine (Box 231, Folder 5)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1978-09 (Box 231, Folder 6)
  - 9-78-001 to 9-78-063, 1978-09 (Box 231, Folder 7)
  - 9-78-064 to 9-78-118, 1978-09 (Box 232, Folder 1)
  - 9-78-119 to 9-78-177, 1978-09 (Box 232, Folder 2)
  - 9-78-178 to 9-78-226, 1978-09 (Box 232, Folder 3)
  - 9-78-227 to 9-78-291, 1978-09 (Box 232, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1978-10 (Box 232, Folder 5)
  - October 1978 Central magazine (Box 232, Folder 6)
  - Slides and transparency, 1978-10 (Box 232, Folder 7)
  - 10-78-001 to 10-78-061, 1978-10 (Box 233, Folder 1)
  - 10-78-062 to 10-78-123, 1978-10 (Box 233, Folder 2)
  - 10-78-124 to 10-78-193, 1978-10 (Box 233, Folder 3)
  - 10-78-194 to 10-78-260, 1978-10 (Box 233, Folder 4)
  - 10-78-263 to 10-78-337, 1978-10 (Box 233, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1978-11 (Box 234, Folder 1)
  - November 1978 Central magazine (Box 234, Folder 2)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1978-11 (Box 234, Folder 3)
  - 11-78-001 to 11-78-059, 1978-11 (Box 234, Folder 4)
  - 11-78-060 to 11-78-121, 1978-11 (Box 234, Folder 5)
  - 11-78-122 to 11-78-179, 1978-11 (Box 234, Folder 6)
  - 11-78-180 to 11-78-235, 1978-11 (Box 234, Folder 7)
  - 11-78-236 to 11-78-302, 1978-11 (Box 235, Folder 1)
  - 11-78-303 to 11-78-367, 1978-11 (Box 235, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1978-12 (Box 235, Folder 3)
  - December 1978 Central magazine (Box 235, Folder 4)
  - 12-78-001 to 12-78-055, 1978-12 (Box 235, Folder 5)
  - 12-78-056 to 12-78-111, 1978-12 (Box 235, Folder 6)
  - 12-78-112 to 12-78-169, 1978-12 (Box 236, Folder 1)
  - 12-78-170 to 12-78-218, 1978-12 (Box 236, Folder 2)
  - 12-78-219 to 12-78-273, 1978-12 (Box 236, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1979-01 (Box 236, Folder 4)
  - January 1979 Central magazine (Box 236, Folder 5)
  - Slides, transparencies and memorandum, 1979-01 (Box 236, Folder 6)
  - 1-79-001 to 1-79-058, 1979-01 (Box 236, Folder 7)
  - 1-79-059 to 1-79-123, 1979-01 (Box 237, Folder 1)
  - 1-79-124 to 1-79-188, 1979-01 (Box 237, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1979-02 (Box 237, Folder 3)
  - February 1979 Central magazine (Box 237, Folder 4)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1979-02 (Box 237, Folder 5)
  - 2-79-002 to 2-79-069, 1979-02 (Box 237, Folder 6)
  - 2-79-071 to 2-79-140, 1979-02 (Box 237, Folder 7)
  - 2-79-141 to 2-79-212, 1979-02 (Box 238, Folder 1)
  - 2-79-213 to 2-79-287, 1979-02 (Box 238, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1979-03 (Box 238, Folder 3)
  - March 1979 Central magazine (Box 238, Folder 4)
  - Slides, transparencies and negatives, 1979-03 (Box 238, Folder 5)
  - 3-79-001 to 3-79-067, 1979-03 (Box 238, Folder 6)
  - 3-79-068 to 3-79-122, 1979-03 (Box 238, Folder 7)
  - 3-79-123 to 3-79-189, 1979-03 (Box 239, Folder 1)
  - 3-79-190 to 3-79-258, 1979-03 (Box 239, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1979-04 (Box 239, Folder 3)
  - April 1979 Central magazine, 1979-04 (Box 239, Folder 4)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1979-04 (Box 239, Folder 5)
  - 4-79-001 to 4-79-068 examples of May 1898 issue used for photo, 1979-04 (Box 239, Folder 6)
  - 4-79-069 to 4-79-127, 1979-04 (Box 239, Folder 7)
  - 4-79-128 to 4-79-189, 1979-04 (Box 240, Folder 1)
  - 4-79-190 to 4-79-253, 1979-04 (Box 240, Folder 2)
  - 4-79-254 to 4-79-325, 1979-04 (Box 240, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1979-05 (Box 240, Folder 4)
  - May 1979 Central magazine (Box 240, Folder 5)
  - 5-79-001 to 5-79-053, 1979-05 (Box 240, Folder 6)
  - 5-79-054 to 5-79-112, 1979-05 (Box 241, Folder 1)
  - 5-79-113 to 5-79-174, 1979-05 (Box 241, Folder 2)
  - 5-79-175 to 5-79-230, 1979-05 (Box 241, Folder 3)
  - 5-79-231 to 5-79-285, 1979-05 (Box 241, Folder 4)
  - 5-79-286 to 5-79-348, 1979-05 (Box 241, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1979-06 (Box 242, Folder 1)
  - June 1979 Central magazine (Box 242, Folder 2)
  - Slides and transparency, 1979-06 (Box 242, Folder 3)
  - 6-79-001 to 6-79-086, 1979-06 (Box 242, Folder 4)
  - 6-79-084 to 6-79-143, 1979-06 (Box 242, Folder 5)
  - 6-79-144 to 6-79-197, 1979-06 (Box 242, Folder 6)
  - 6-79-198 to 6-79-257, 1979-06 (Box 242, Folder 7)
  - 6-79-258 to 6-79-308, 1979-06 (Box 243, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1979-07 (Box 243, Folder 2)
  - July 1979 Central magazine (Box 243, Folder 3)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1979-07 (Box 243, Folder 4)
  - 7-79-002 to 7-79-063, 1979-07 (Box 243, Folder 5)
  - 7-79-064 to 7-79-119, 1979-07 (Box 243, Folder 6)
  - 7-79-120 to 7-79-184, 1979-07 (Box 243, Folder 7)
  - 7-79-185 to 7-79-246, 1979-07 (Box 244, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1979-08 (Box 244, Folder 2)
  - August 1979 Central magazine (Box 244, Folder 3)
  - Slides, 1979-08 (Box 244, Folder 4)
  - 8-79-001 to 8-79-061, 1979-08 (Box 244, Folder 5)
  - 8-79-062 to 8-79-111, 1979-08 (Box 244, Folder 6)
  - 8-79-112 to 8-79-173, 1979-08 (Box 244, Folder 7)
  - 8-79-174 to 8-79-231, 1979-08 (Box 245, Folder 1)
  - 8-79-233 to 8-79-287, 1979-08 (Box 245, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1979-09 (Box 245, Folder 3)
  - September 1979 Central magazine (Box 245, Folder 4)
  - Slides, and transparencies, "scotch prints", 1979-09 (Box 245, Folder 5)
  - 9-79-001 to 9-79-059, 1979-09 (Box 245, Folder 6)
  - 9-79-060 to 9-79-113, 1979-09 (Box 245, Folder 7)
  - 9-79-114 to 9-79-175, 1979-09 (Box 246, Folder 1)
  - 9-79-176 to 9-79-238, 1979-09 (Box 246, Folder 2)
  - 9-79-239 to 9-79-296, 1979-09 (Box 246, Folder 3)
  - 9-79-297 to 9-79-359, 1979-09 (Box 246, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1979-10 (Box 246, Folder 5)
  - Slides, transparencies, and memorandum, 1979-10 (Box 246, Folder 6)
  - October 1979 Central magazine (Box 246, Folder 7)
  - 10-79-001 to 10-79-059, 1979-10 (Box 247, Folder 1)
  - 10-79-060 to 10-79-128, 1979-10 (Box 247, Folder 2)
  - 10-79-130 to 10-79-186, 1979-10 (Box 247, Folder 3)
  - 10-79-188 to 10-79-255, 1979-10 (Box 247, Folder 4)
  - 10-79-257 to 10-79-316, 1979-10 (Box 247, Folder 5)
  - 10-79-317 to 10-79-374, 1979-10 (Box 248, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1979-11 (Box 248, Folder 2)
  - November 1979 Central magazine (Box 248, Folder 3)
  - Slides, 1979-11 (Box 248, Folder 4)
  - 11-79-001 to 11-79-067, 1979-11 (Box 248, Folder 5)
  - 11-79-068 to 11-79-124, 1979-11 (Box 248, Folder 6)
  - 11-79-125 to 11-79-171, 1979-11 (Box 248, Folder 7)
  - 11-79-173 to 11-79-237, 1979-11 (Box 249, Folder 1)
  - 11-79-238 to 11-79-293, 1979-11 (Box 249, Folder 2)
  - 11-79-294 to 11-79-344, 1979-11 (Box 249, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1979-12 (Box 249, Folder 4)
  - December 1979 Central magazine (Box 249, Folder 5)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1979-12 (Box 249, Folder 6)
  - 12-79-001 to 12-79-061, 1979-12 (Box 249, Folder 7)
  - 12-79-062 to 12-79-097, 1979-12 (Box 250, Folder 1)
  - 12-79-098 to 12-79-161, 1979-12 (Box 250, Folder 2)
  - 12-79-162 to 12-79-210, 1979-12 (Box 250, Folder 3)
  - 12-79-211 to 12-79-259, 1979-12 (Box 250, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1980-01 (Box 250, Folder 5)
  - January 1980 Central magazine (Box 250, Folder 6)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1980-01 (Box 250, Folder 7)
  - 1-80-001 to 1-80-053, 1980-01 (Box 251, Folder 1)
  - 1-80-054 to 1-80-114, 1980-01 (Box 251, Folder 2)
  - 1-80-115 to 1-80-158, 1980-01 (Box 251, Folder 3)
  - 1-80-159 to 1-80-214, 1980-01 (Box 251, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1980-02 (Box 251, Folder 5)
  - February 1980 Central magazine (Box 251, Folder 6)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1980-02 (Box 251, Folder 7)
  - 2-80-001 to 2-80-064, 1980-02 (Box 252, Folder 1)